https://www.firstmidag.com/privacy-policy/

Your Source for
Farm Management, Farm Brokerage/Auctions,
Privacy Policy
Thank you for viewing our Privacy statement.
Visitors to First Mid Ag Services will remain anonymous.  We do not collect personal identifying information about visitors to our site.
Our servers collect standard non-identifying information about visits to the site, such as date and time visited, IP address (which is a numerical identifier for your computer while it is accessing the internet), city, state and country.  This information is used to compile standard statistics on site usage.
If you have provided personal identifying information via e-mail (such as name and address), the information will only be used to communicate with you to handle your request.  It is not sold or transferred to other parties.
First Mid Ag Services is committed to protecting your privacy.
Concerns about this site should be directed to:
Justin Wheeler
First Mid Ag Services
455 North Main Street
Decatur, IL 62523
Phone: 217-421-9615
jwheeler@firstmid.comjwheeler@soybank.com
Please Note: If you are sending electronic mail to First Mid Ag Services we want to remind you that email is not necessarily secure against interception. If your information is very sensitive, or includes personal or confidential information--such as your bank account, charge card, or social security number--you may want to send it by postal mail to one of the addresses listed on this Web site.
NOTICE OF YOUR FINANCIAL PRIVACY RIGHTS
We, our, and us means First Mid Ag Services.
This is our privacy notice for our customers. When we use the words ”you” and ”your” we mean the following types of customers:
All of our consumer customers who have a continuing relationship with us, such as:
Farm Management Services
Real Estate Brokerage
Appraisal Services
Ag Project Consultation
Commodity Consultation
We will tell you the sources for nonpublic personal information we collect on our customers. We will tell you what measures we take to secure that information.
We first define some terms.
Nonpublic personal information means
information about you that we collect in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. Nonpublic personal information does not include information that is available from public sources, such as telephone directories or government records.
An affiliate is a company we own or control, a company that owns or controls us, or a company that is owned or controlled by the same company that owns or controls us. Ownership does not mean complete ownership, but means owning enough to have control.
A nonaffiliated third party is a person we do not employ or a company that is not an affiliate of ours. This is also known as nonaffiliated third party, or simply an "other party"
THE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on applications or other forms
Information about your transactions with us
Information about your transactions with nonaffiliated third parties
Information from a consumer reporting agency
INFORMATION WE DISCLOSE ABOUT YOU
We do NOT disclose any nonpublic personal information about you to anyone, except as permitted by law.
THE CONFIDENTIALITY, SECURITY AND INTEGRITY OF YOUR NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.
YOUR INFORMATION WITH OTHER PARTIES
We will not disclose information about you to anyone except as disclosed in this policy or as permitted by law. This might include disclosures necessary to service your account, perform joint marketing or prevent unauthorized transactions.
NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION AND FORMER CUSTOMERS
We do not disclose nonpublic personal information about former customers, except as permitted by law.
AUTHORIZED SHARING
We share information within First Mid Companies Family so that our affiliates can work together to meet your financial needs. We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, with our affiliated banks and companies including: financial service providers such as mortgage bankers, insurance agents, securities brokers-dealers, and farm managers.
By law, information that helps us identify you or is derived from your transactions and experiences with us may be shared within the First Mid Companies family.
AUTHORIZED SHARING - OUTSIDE MARKETING SERVICES
We may disclose the following information to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf:
Information you give us on an application or other form such as:
Name
Address
We disclose the information listed above with companies that perform marketing services on our behalf. We may also disclose information about you to other outside marketing services as permitted by law. Here are the types of businesses with whom we may disclose information for outside marketing purposes:
Service providers that perform marketing services for us such as direct sales companies
We may disclose information about you to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf to provide you with information about additional products and services.
Our Vision
To be a nimble, community banking team committed to quality and growth for the benefit of all our stakeholders.
Our Mission
To fulfill the financial needs of our communities with exceptional personal service, professionalism and integrity, and deliver meaningful value and results for customers and shareholders.
Navigate
staff profiles
bloomington, il principal office
decatur, il regional office
kankakee, il regional office
mattoon, il regional office
peoria, il regional office
Springfield, il regional office
